const networkComponents = 
[
            {
                question: "What is Computer Network Components?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "Equipment gadget that splits the organization association between different gadgets.",
                    choice2: "Embrace each physical elements and also the software system needed to put in pc networks in each organizations and houses.",
                    choice3: "That offer even as get administrations from totally different companions in a very workgroup network.",
                    choice4: "A gadget that adds 3G or 4G (LTE) cell network to PCs, PCs and different tablets."
                },
                answer: 'choice2',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/advantages.html?topickey=adv&item=0"
            },

            {
                question: "What are the two types of NIC?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "Cables and Connectors",
                    choice2: "Switch and Router",
                    choice3: "Wired and Wireless",
                    choice4: "Hub and Modem"
                },
                answer: 'choice3',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/hub.html?topickey=mc&item=2"
            },
            {
                question: "What is Switch mean?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "an equipment gadget which is utilized to associate a LAN with a web",
                    choice2: "is an equipment gadget that permits the PC to associate with the web over the current phone line.",
                    choice3: "is a transmission media utilized for communicating a sign.",
                    choice4: "is an equipment gadget that associates different gadgets on a PC organization."
                },
                answer: 'choice4',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/router.html?topickey=mc&item=5"
            },
            {
                question: "What is Router mean?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "is a transmission media utilized for communicating a sign.",
                    choice2: "is an equipment gadget that permits the PC to associate with the web over the current phone line.",
                    choice3: "an equipment gadget which is utilized to associate a LAN with a web association.",
                    choice4: "is an equipment gadget that associates different gadgets on a PC organization."
                },
                answer: 'choice3',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/advantages-of-router.html?topickey=mc&item=7"
            },
            {
                question: "What is the advantage of Router?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "Causes you to share printers, scanners, and email.",
                    choice2: "Causes you to share data at exceptionally quick speed.",
                    choice3: "Security:Â The data which is communicated to the organization will navigate the whole link, yet the lone determined gadget which has been tended to can peruse the information.",
                    choice4: "Electronic correspondence is more productive and more affordable than without the network."
                },
                answer: 'choice3',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/modem.html?topickey=mc&item=9"
            },
            {
                question: "What is Modem?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "is an equipment gadget that permits the PC to associate with the web over the current phone line.",
                    choice2: "is a transmission media utilized for communicating a sign",
                    choice3: "is an equipment gadget that associates different gadgets on a PC organization.",
                    choice4: "Electronic correspondence is more productive and more affordable than without the network."
                },
                answer: 'choice1',
                nextPath: "./../../module1/networkcomponents/cable&connectors.html?topickey=mc&item=11"
            },
            {
                question: "What is Cable and Connectors mean?",
                choices: {
                    choice1: "is a transmission media utilized for communicating a sign.",
                    choice2: "is an equipment gadget that permits the PC to associate with the web over the current phone line.",
                    choice3: "an equipment gadget which is utilized to associate a LAN with a web association.",
                    choice4: "is an equipment gadget that associates different gadgets on a PC organization."
                },
                answer: 'choice1',
                nextPath: "./../index.html",
                last: {
                    titleUnlock: 'Types of Network',
                    finishedKey: 'cnc'
                }
            },
] 
            
const internetwork = [
    {
        question: "What is acronym for LAN?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Locale Area Networking",
            choice2: "Local Area Networking",
            choice3: "Local Access Network",
            choice4: "Local  Area Network "
        },
        answer: 'choice4',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/quiz.html?topickey=lan&item=2&quiz=1"
    },
    {
        question: "Define what is LAN?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "A private network dependent on the internet protocol.",
            choice2: "A group of computers connected to each other in a small area.",
            choice3: "A network organized within an individual person.",
            choice4: "A network that reaches out over an enormous geological area."
        },
        answer: 'choice2',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/pan.html?topickey=pan&item=0"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the scientist researcher that brings the idea of PAN?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Marcus Zimmerman",
            choice2: "Thomas Zimmerman",
            choice3: "Thomas Edison",
            choice4: "George Zimmerman",
        },
        answer: 'choice2',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/wan.html?topickey=wan&item=0"
    },
    {
        question: "Wide Area Network is larger than the LAN?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "True",
            choice2: "False",
        },
        answer: 'choice1',
    nextPath: "./../../module1/quiz.html?topickey=wan&item=2&quiz=4"
    },
    {
        question: "One of the largest Wide Area network?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Last Mile",
            choice2: "Intranet",
            choice3: "Internet",
            choice4: "Mobile Broadband",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/wan-2.html?topickey=wan&item=3"
    },
    {
        question: "These are the Advantages of Wide Area Network?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "High Bandwidth,  Get updated files, Geographical Area",
            choice2: "High Bandwidth, Sharing of software and resources, Time saving",
            choice3: "Geographical Area, Time saving, High Bandwidth",
            choice4: "High Bandwidth, Collaboration, Communication",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/wan-3.html?topickey=wan&item=5"
    },
    {
        question: "Types of Network are categories by their Geographical Area Cover?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "True",
            choice2: "False",
        },
        answer: 'choice1',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/man.html?topickey=man&item=0"
    },
    {
        question: "What is acronym MAN stands for?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Metropolitan Access Network ",
            choice2: "Multi-Area Network",
            choice3: "Metropolitan Area Network",
            choice4: "Metropolitan Area Net",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/internetwork.html?topickey=in&item=0"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the types of Internetwork?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Ultranet and Internet",
            choice2: "Intranet and Ultranet",
            choice3: "Extranet and Intranet",
            choice4: "Extranet and Internet",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/types-of-network/internetwork-2.html?topickey=in&item=2"
    },
    {
        question: "What are the three common types of Computer Networks?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "RAM, LAN, WAN",
            choice2: "MAN, BAN, WAN",
            choice3: "MAN, LAN, WAN",
            choice4: "None of the Above",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../index.html",
        last: {
            titleUnlock: 'OSI vs TCP/IP Model',
            finishedKey: 'top'
        }
    },
   

]

const tcpip = [
    {
        question: "In TCP/IP model this layer is responsible for message segmentation, flow control and correction that establishes basic data channels that application, use for task-specific data exchange. What called in this layer?",
       choices: {
        choice1: "Link layer",
        choice2: "Application layer",
        choice3: "Transport layer ",
        choice4: "Internet Layer",
       },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/quiz.html?topickey=quiz&item=1&quiz=1"
    },
    {
        question: "What layer in OSI model that accountable for the transmission and reception of unstructured information between a tool and a physical transmission medium?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Link layer",
            choice2: "Application layer",
            choice3: "Transport layer ",
            choice4: "Internet Layer",
        },
        answer: 'choice4',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/quiz.html?topickey=quiz&item=2&quiz=2"
    },
    {
        question: "It is accountable for the character code translation, conversion, compression, and cryptography. What called this layer in OSI Model?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Data layer",
            choice2: "Application layer",
            choice3: "Presentation layer",
            choice4: "Session Layer",
        },
        answer: 'choice3',
        nextPath: "./../../module1/quiz.html?topickey=quiz&item=3&quiz=3"
    },
    {
        question: "What layer combine the physical and data link layers where functions into a single layer. Including all hosts accessible without traversing a router?",
        choices: {
            choice1: "Application layer",
            choice2: "Internet layer",
            choice3: "Session Layer",
            choice4: "Link Layer",
        },
        answer: 'choice4',
        nextPath: "./../index.html",
        last: {
            titleUnlock: 'Domain Name System (DNS)',
            finishedKey: 'osi'
        }
    },
]


export { networkComponents, internetwork, tcpip}